factorydirect.ca 2017-06-06

# Canada’s best deals on unlocked apple and android cell phones, TVs, tablets, android media players, air conditioners, fidget spinners, kitchen appliances, bathroom accessories, as seen on tv products, gazeebos, tents and more

## **WHAT INFORMATION DOES FACTORYDIRECT.CA COLLECT?**

Factorydirect.ca collects personal information from our customers.  This information typically includes the customer’s name, address, postal code, phone number, and email address.  A customer is not obliged to provide personal information*, however factorydirect.ca may not be able to provide products, service or information required with such information.

*If the customer is signing up for factorydirect.ca “email blast” on the website an email address is mandatory.  If the customer is applying for a Mail in Rebate, they must provide all the required personal information in order to receive the cheque.

## **HOW IS THE INFORMATION USED?**

With the customer’s consent in providing the information, factorydirect.ca uses the information for a variety of reasons including (but not limited to):

  * To assist our marketing department in determining where our customer base is coming from which allows factorydirect.ca to better serve our customers and to distribute future flyers more efficiently.

A customer’s information is not used or disclosed for purposes other than those set out herein, no is the information shared with third parties, such as for the sale of mailing lists.

## **WHAT IS CONSENT?**

A customer’s knowledge and consent is required for the collection, use or disclosure of their personal information except as required by law.  During sales transactions, our employees may request the personal information set above, and by providing us with the information, the customer is consenting to our use of such information purposes set out herein.  When a customer fills out their information to subscribe to factorydirect.ca’s email blast, or to fill out a Mail in Rebate application, the customer is offering their consent.

## **HOW DO WE KEEP A CUSTOMER’S INFORMATION SAFE?**

The security of a customer’s personal information is a big priority for factorydirect.ca.  factorydirect.ca maintains reasonable safeguards and appropriate security standards to protect a customer’s personal information against disclosure or misuse, which include: storage on access-restricted computer files that are password protected; and restrict access to the information to only the Mail in Rebate staff, and to Head Office managers.

## **HOW LONG IS THE INFORMATION RETAINED?**

Personal information is retained only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and reasonable time thereafter, or to meet legal requirements.

Factorydirect.ca destroys a customer’s information or makes it anonymous when it is no longer required for the purposes for which it was collected.

A customer may request that the personal information be removed from our records subject to our requirements for continued retention of their information for warranty or exchange purposes, and factorydirect.ca will make every reasonable effort to meet a customer’s request.

## **HOW CAN YOU INSURE THAT YOUR INFORMATION IS CORRECT?**

At any time, a customer may request access to their personal information to verify the accuracy and completeness thereof and have it amended appropriately.  Factorydirect.ca will try to accommodate all requests for access within hours of the request.

### **FURTHER QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**

You may direct any questions or concerns to:

  * Factorydirect.ca Privacy Office
  * 501 Applewood Cres
  * Concord, Ontario
  * L4K 4J3
  * Tel: 905-660-5030
  * Fax: 905-660-9793
  * Factorydirect.ca will respond to your questions or concerns as quickly as possible.

### **PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

This privacy policy is subject to change as factorydirect.ca continues to modify and improve our practices and policies in order to serve the interests of our customers.

*We currently only ship out deals within Canada from our Ontario distribution warehouse.  
Discounted shipping may be available on larger orders - please contact us for specific requests.  
Wholesale volume prices may be available to qualified resellers excluding  
product deals that are offered on sale, coupon or special promotion. 

*Prices & availability are subject to change without notice.

factorydirect.ca is not responsible for typographical errors or omissions.  
Product images are for representation only, Product may not be exactly as shown.   
Trademarks and logos are properties of their respective owners.   
factorydirect and factorydirect.ca are registered business names of Rlogistics Limited Partnership.  
501 Applewood Crescent , Concord, Ontario, Canada L4K 4J3. 1-866-907-7788.
